ann-angel.com 2017-12-01

# PRIVACY POLICY/ 2257 / REFUND POLICY | Ann Angel Sexy cam girl and pornstar hottie goes hardcore

In support of our excellence in customer service, we’re a proud member of the network.

We are committed to protecting your privacy. The following information is designed to help you understand how we collect, use, disseminate and safeguard the information you provide to us while accessing and using our Site. By accessing and using our Site, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our information practices, please do not access or use our Site. As provided below, we reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, add or remove portions of this policy at any time by posting such changes to this page. Such changes will be effective upon posting. Adult Staffing requests that you read this Privacy Policy carefully and consult it regularly.

**Information Collection and Use  **

We are the sole owner of the information collected on the Site such as names and e-mail addresses. Information is collected through the processing by way of an on-line registration form. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others.

**Registration and On-line Forms**

In order to complete a registration form, a user must complete an on-line form. This form requires a user to provide us with certain contact information (including but not limited to your name and e-mail address). If we have trouble processing a registration form or otherwise need to contact a user, the user’s contact information will be used to get in touch with them. From time to time, we may also ask that you provide us with additional information so that we can better tailor our services to meet your needs.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. We will use cookies to identify the most popular areas of our Site and to determine the effectiveness of our promotional activities. Additionally, we reserve the right to disclose this data to advertisers to inform them of the number of people who have seen and/or clicked through their advertisements. Please note that some of our business partners may also use cookies on our Site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

**Sharing**

We do not currently sell or otherwise make available personally identifiable information about our users to third parties. Nevertheless, we reserve the right to make such information available to third parties in the future in order to enhance and personalize our services, or in the case of bankruptcy, sale of an asset, business or division, a merger or acquisition, or similar change of ownership.

**Law Enforcement**

We will cooperate with law enforcement authorities, private-party litigants, and others seeking information about our end users to the extent required by applicable law. Examples of such cooperation include compliance with discovery requests, subpoenas, court orders and writs.

**Links**

This Site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware that when they leave our Site they should read the privacy statements of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information.

**Security**

We agree to use commercially reasonable efforts to protect the information you have provided to us from unauthorized access by using encryption and other security measures. We encourage you to contact us if you are interested in learning more about our security measures.

**Children**

Our Site is not intended for children under the age of eighteen (18). Our Site does not target children, nor do we solicit data, or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from them. We encourage parents and legal guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate in the interactive activities offered on the sites their children visit.

**Correction/Updating Personal Information**

If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as email address), or if a user no longer desires our service, you should contact us to correct, update, or delete this information.

**Choice  **

From time to time, we may send our users e-mail or other notices regarding new services, promotions, or other information which may be of general interest. Users who no longer wish to receive materials from us may opt-out of receiving these communications by choosing a do not contact option or by contacting us. We will comply will all requests for removal.

**Notification of Changes**

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting such changes on our Site. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective upon posting such changes. If you access or use our Site, you are required to periodically check our Privacy Policy for any changes. If you continue to access or use our Site after we have changed our Privacy Policy, you manifest your assent to the changes to our Privacy Policy.

If we decide to use your personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated in the Privacy Policy at the time that such information was collected, we will attempt to notify you of such changes. You agree that if we send you an e-mail to the e-mail address reflected in our records, such e-mail will constitute acceptable notice to you of the change in our policy. The notice will provide you with an opportunity to “opt-out” so that we may not use your personally identifiable information in a manner which is different from the manner described at the time that you provided us with such information. If you do not affirmatively “opt-out” pursuant to the instructions provided to you in the notice, then you agree that we may use your personally identifiable information in the manner described in the notice. (If we have no e-mail address for you, or if we do not have a current e-mail address for you, then you agree that adequate notice of the change in our policy will be effected by posting such a change onto our Privacy Policy, which shall also disclose information about how you may “opt-out” so that we may not use your personally identifiable information in a manner which is materially different from the manner described at the time that you provided us with such information. If you do not affirmatively “opt-out” pursuant to the instructions posted within the time period specified, then you agree that we may use your personally identifiable information as described in the posted notice).

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or if you otherwise need to contact us regarding your personally identifiable information, contact us by sending an e-mail. Please provide us with your name and e-mail address so we can service you quicker.

Please send your e-mail to: SUPPORT@DIGIAIMG.COM

**CUSTODIAN OF RECORDS – U.S.C. TITLE 18,  
SECTION 2257 COMPLIANCE**

In compliance with United States Code, Title 18, Section 2257, all models, actors, actresses and other persons who appear in any visual depiction of sexually explicit content, simulated sexual content, tease content, non-nude content, nude content or other content appearing or otherwise contained in or at this site were over the age of eighteen years at the time of the creation of such depictions. Records required to be maintained pursuant to U.S.C. Title 18, Section 2257 are kept by the custodian of records and are available to the Attorney General for inspection

**Digital Angel Images LLC  
PO BOX 09054  
Staten Island, NY, 10309-9054**

Please email for inspection address: **support@digiaimg.com**

For more information regarding Model Age Verification, please contact us at  
**support@digiaimg.com**

**Digital Angel Images LLC**. is the primary producer and owner (as the term is defined in 18 USC section 2257)  
of any of the visual content contained in the web site.

Refund Policy  
Refunds are provided upon request.
